{
    "subject": "resource/Arthur_Wilkinson",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "British composer",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Wilkinson is a British composer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.85882169008255,
            "question": "What kind of music does Arthur Wilkinson compose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8320225477218628,
            "question": "Are there any famous compositions by Arthur Wilkinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6798703074455261,
            "question": "Is Arthur Wilkinson known for his work in music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.654679536819458,
            "question": "What profession does Arthur Wilkinson have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6135929822921753,
            "question": "What nationality is Arthur Wilkinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6110382676124573,
            "question": "Has Arthur Wilkinson collaborated with other musicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4010375738143921,
            "question": "Where was Arthur Wilkinson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34663403034210205,
            "question": "What musical training does Arthur Wilkinson have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.336845338344574,
            "question": "When was Arthur Wilkinson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32301825284957886,
            "question": "Has Arthur Wilkinson won any awards for his music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Wilkinson is a British composer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1071_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Arthur Wilkinson born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1071_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical training does Arthur Wilkinson have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1071_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Arthur Wilkinson born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1071_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1071_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1071_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1071_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1071_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1071_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1071_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1071_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1071_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1071_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1071_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. In particular, the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1071/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt states that Arthur Wilkinson was a composer, and the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1071/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt describes him as the composer of Three Rivers Fantasy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Arthur Wilkinson being a British composer, including his contributions to film, stage shows, and television. Therefore, the statement that Arthur Wilkinson is a British composer is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}